(Penny:)So far, the future's great.
(Stuart:)Hey, can I go to the bathroom?
(Raj:)Fine, just try not to look too alive.
(Stuart:)That's my jam.
(Bernadette:)So one of us went back
in time to kill Stuart?
(Amy:)-But why?
-Perhaps this will help.
(Raj:)Here are some facts
about yourselves in the future
(Raj:)that might contain a clue.
(Amy:)Hey, I won
the Nobel Prize in physiology.
(Amy:)Then I used the money to buy
Stuart's comic book store,
(Amy:)and close it down so Sheldon
would pay attention to me.
(Amy:)Not the worst idea.
(Penny:)Hey, I'm a famous actress
living in London.
(Leonard:)I'm a professor at Stanford.
(Bernadette:)So I guess you two are
making it work long distance.
Oh, ho. In this game,
as your careers both took off,
(Raj:)you drifted apart.
Kind of like how future me
(Raj:)lost touch with you guys
after I became boy toy
(Raj:)for the wrinkled,
but still flexible, Madonna.